stinkyinkshop.co.uk 2013-05-08

# Stinkyink Privacy Policy

Stinkyink is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of consumers of its interactive products and services. The following statement discloses the privacy practices for the Stinkyink websites and attempts to address the following questions:

  * What personal information we collect and how is it used
  * Who will have access to this personal information
  * What are cookies and how are they used
  * What choices are available to a user regarding the disclosure of personal information
  * How can a user access, update, or delete his/her information
  * Who can a user contact if they have any questions regarding privacy

Stinkyink.com is a multi-dimensional Website. It offers its users an array of services. Because the success of Stinkyink is dependent on building and maintaining goodwill with our customers, we are committed to implementing measures designed to protect the privacy of those using our services. Moreover, we see it as our responsibility to set examples and help establish the standards for privacy on the Internet. During registration, each service asks the user to provide different types and amounts of personal information. We intend through the use of this statement to illustrate, clarify, and reinforce the degree of security and privacy an internet-user should feel when accessing the Stinkyink.com Website.

This Privacy Policy governs your interaction with the Stinkyink website, and your registration for and use of Stinkyink's online services. Except as set forth within this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service and other published guidelines, we do not release personally identifiable information about out members and visitors without their permission. Please note that Stinkyink reviews its privacy practices from time to time, and that those practices are therefore subject to change. We ask that you bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our Privacy Policy. After reading this policy, if there are any further questions regarding Stinkyink privacy practices please feel free to address all inquires to info@Stinkyink.com

## Personal Information and Its Use

**Stinkyink gathers two types of information about users:**

### (1) Non-personally identifiable information:

When visitors come to our website, we collect and aggregate information indicating, among other things, which pages were visited, the order in which they were visited, and which hyperlinks were "clicked." Collecting such information involves the logging of IP addresses, operating system and browser software used by each visitor to the Stinkyink website.

Although such information is not personally identifiable, we can determine from the IP address a visitor's Internet Service Provider and the geographic location of his or her point of connectivity. The non-personally identifiable information we collect helps us identify the most popular areas of our website and determine the effectiveness of our promotional activities. In addition, we may disclose some of this information to advertisers to inform them of the number of people who have seen and/or clicked through their advertisements.

### (2) Personally identifiable information:

In certain areas of the Stinkyink website. during our signup process we will ask a user to provide his/her full name, and contact details. Stinkyink collects this personal information primarily so we can complete and deliver your order to you. We may provide the information provided in the delivery details section with 3rd party couriers and delivery agencies in order to facilitate the delivery of your purchase.

## Information Collecting and Access

The information that a user shares with Stinkyink is collected, stored, and handled carefully by Stinkyink. However, Stinkyink may offer some of its services in conjunction with partner companies which may need access to your details to fulfil your order. We will endeavour to make it clear whenever this is the case.

## Cookies

Stinkyink aids in offering its community members a simple, easy, and personalised web experience through the use of cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Stinkyink uses cookies for the benefit of its users. For example, to make the log in process for the Stinkyink website easier and faster, users have the option to save their ID and password in a cookie. The next time the user logs into a Stinkyink service, he/she will be able to use one-click instant access.

Cookies help us determine the type of content and sites to which you link, the length of time you spend at any particular area of the site, and the services you choose to use. Cookies also tell us which advertising you have seen on our site. Essentially, cookies are your identification cards for the Stinkyink servers, that placed them there. Cookies are only read by the server that placed them, and are unable to execute any code or virus. Cookies allow us to serve you better and more efficiently, and to personalize your experience at the Stinkyink website. Nevertheless, you should be able to control how and whether cookies will be accepted by your web browser. For more information on how to do so, please refer to the documentation accompanying your browser. In essence, Stinkyink views the use of its cookies as a "luxurious tool" which enables its user to move freely from service to service without the hassle of having to "re-identify" themselves.

You can find out more about how we use cookies on our Cookie Policy page

## Information Choices

Stinkyink users always have a choice whether or not to disclose information. Certain information is required for registration of our services, but most other requested information is optional. It is a top priority at Stinkyink to make its user feel comfortable and in control.

## Links

This website may contain links to other websites. Stinkyink is not responsible for the content or the privacy policy or practices of any other websites or for the actions of the companies responsible for those websites. Please review the privacy policies of those websites before providing them with any personal information.

## Update and Access of Information

Stinkyink strongly encourages its members to update and edit their personal information and keep it current. A Stinkyink user can easily access and correct his/her personal information at any time using our web based interface.

## Contact

We may revise our privacy policy from time to time. When we do, those changes will be reflected in this document. Any changes that we make will always be made with your privacy and satisfaction as top priorities. We encourage you to review our privacy policy whenever you visit this website. 

Questions regarding this statement or the privacy practices of Stinkyink should be directed to the Stinkyink site coordinator at info@Stinkyink.com

Stinkyink users also have the option of directly contacting our customer service department via telephone, fax, and/or standard mail.

We feel we have a duty to provide our members with a safe, secure, and private website. The Stinkyink name and reputation is at the crux of our business, and we will take all necessary actions to uphold and reinforce our strong standing as a leading online printer consumables website.

## Copyright Policy

Stinkyink owns or has the right to use all the intellectual propriety rights with respect to the content and services that are developed or jointly developed by Stinkyink. This content and services are protected by applicable intellectual property laws, copyrights, trademarks, service marks, patents or other proprietary rights and laws.

For permission on copyright or any question, please contact info@Stinkyink.com

  * About Stinkyink What we do and how we do it
  * The Stinkyink Story How we got where we are today
  * Meet the Team It's all about the people baby!
  * Testimonials See why our customers love us
  * FAQ's Frequently Asked Questions
  * Delivery Options You'll get your ink, in a blink!
  * Payment Methods Pay the easy way with Stinkyink!
  * Safe Shopping How we protect you from nasties
  * Quality StatementsOnly the highest quality
  * EventsMeet us on the road
  * Press RoomGet the Scoop on Stinkyink
  * Terms & Conditions All the small print
  * Privacy Policy How we use your information
  * Cookie Policy Cookies - not just for snacking!
